http://www.plastechprint.co.uk/about-us/privacy-notice/

Expand/collapse navigation
HomeAbout Us Find UsBrochure DownloadTerms and ConditionsPrivacy NoticeContact UsOur Products Badges & Identification Button BadgesChalkboard BadgesConference Name BadgesDesk Name PlatesFlexi TagsName BadgesInstabadge EssentialInstabadge LiteInstabadge PremiumKey FobsLanyardsLuggage TagsMembership CardsOyster Card WalletPlastic Card HoldersPhoto ID CardsTyvek WristbandsSnap Back Badge ReelsWooden BadgesVinyl WristbandsDocument Management Business Card HolderElasticated FoldersFileprong FoldersLetterfilesLever Arch FolderPolypropylene Conference BoxesPolypropylene Carry CasesPolypropylene FoldersPolypropylene Ring BindersPolypropylene WalletsPopper Stud WalletsSwingrip FoldersVinyl ClipboardsZipper WalletsPodiums & Plinths Display PlinthTable Top DisplayTrappa FramePromotional Banners Roller BannersBarracudaDesktopDragonflyEcoGrasshopperMini MosquitoAd FlagBlizzardBlade BannerEyeletted BannerPromotional Plastic Bookmark RulersDesk CalendarsDomed DecalsDoor HangersStickersWrite on Wipe off BoardSubscribe
HomeAbout UsContact UsOur ProductsSubscribe
Plastech Print Ltd
Privacy Notice
At Plastech Print by Badgemaster we are committed to protecting your privacy.
This Privacy Policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from
you,
or that you provide to us, will be processed by us.
For General Data Protection Regulation purposes we are the data controller.
How we collect your information
We collect your information by email, telephone or via options on our website
(ie Contact Form, Sample Request etc). The type of information we may collect about
you
includes, but is not limited to, your name, address, telephone number and email
address.
What we do with it
We use your information to:
* Process your sample requests
* Process your quotation requests
* Process and fulfil your Purchase Orders
* To provide general customer service
* We may check your credit history.
* We may collect card information to process your payment.
* We may use your information to send you direct marketing emails containing
special offers and promotions. You can opt-out at any time.
* We may store your information with our cloud service providers.
* We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit
consent.
* We never have, and will not, sell your information.
Whom we share it with
We share your details with our selected business partners:
* Cloud providers that help us store your information
* IT service providers that help us with our internal IT issues
* Payment service providers that process your payment information on our behalf
* Credit check companies that help us understand your credit history
* Couriers that help deliver our products to you
* Debt Collection Agency / Lawyers representing us in the event of a legal claim
The information we hold will be accurate and up to date.
You can check the information that we hold about you by emailing us.
If you find any inaccuracies we will be more than happy to delete or correct them
promptly.
The personal information which we hold will be held securely in accordance with our
internal security policy and the law.
If you have any questions or comments about privacy, please contact us:
by email mailto:ptpartroom@btconnect.com
via our website - Contact Us | PlasTech Print by Badgemaster, Nottingham
or by post - Hazelford Way Industrial Park, Newstead, Nottingham, NG150DQ
Find UsBrochure DownloadTerms and ConditionsPrivacy Notice
Business Hours
Mon-Fri :
